export const QUESTIONS_DATA = [
  {
    roundTitle: "Round One-Yoga Theory", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "What is meant by Yoga? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Body + Mind(Union)", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "State the Niyamas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Tapassu,Santhosh,Swadhyaya,Soucham,Eshwara Pranidhanam", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "Give an quotation related to health,wealth and character?", type: "BLANK", answer: "If wealth is lost, nothing is lost; If health is lost something is lost; If character is lost, Everything is lost.", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Who was the founder of Yogic science?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Patanjali", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "How many slokas are there in the Bhagavadgitha?", type: "BLANK", answer: "700 or 701", is_answered: false},
    { id: 6, question: "Time period of jaladhouthi?", type: "BLANK", answer: "15DAYS", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "What are the steps of Ashtanga Yoga?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Yama, niyama, Asana, Pranayama, Prathyahara, Dharana, Dhayana, Samadhi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "Which sense differs human beings from other living beings?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Intellect", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "Say any 5 different types of Yoga?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Jnana, Karma, Bhakthi, Mantra, laya, Kundalini, Raja, Hatha", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "What is the Mantra for Asanas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Om Mani Bhrajat…", is_answered: false }]
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Two-EPICS", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "Name the Dasavatharas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Matsya, Kurma, Varaha, Narasimha, Vamana, Parasu Rama,Sri Rama, Sri Krishna, Boudha, Kalki", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "Say any 5 of Saptha Rishis?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Kasyapa, Athri, Bharadwaja, Vishwa mitra, Gowthama, Jamadagni, Vasishta", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "Who are the parents of Hanuman", type: "BLANK", answer: "mother Anjana and father Kesari", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Who were the sons of Ravana?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Meghanada, Atikaya, Akshayakumara, Narantaka, Devantaka, Trishira, and Prahasta", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "Who are the parents of Dattatreya?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Athri – Anasuya", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "According to the Ramayana, for which king did Rishi Vishwamitra create a new Swarga?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Thrishanku", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "Who was the brother of jatayu in Ramayana", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sampati", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "Who is the Guru of Devathas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Bruhaspathi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "Father of Parasurama?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Jamadagni", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "What were the Rakshasa Janmas of Jaya Vijayas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hiranyaksha-Hiranayakasipa,  Ravana-Kumbhakarna, Sisupala – Dantavaktra", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "Who are the parents of Markandeya", type: "BLANK", answer: "Mrikanda and Manasvini", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Three-Yoga Practical", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "State the names of Suryanamaskaras?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Pranama, Hasth uthana, Pada hastha, Ashwa sanchalana, Danda, Ashtanga namaskara, Bhujanga, Parvatha", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "What is the main nadi of 72000 nadis?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sushumna", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "What are the Nitya sadhana Asanas? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sarvanga, Matsya, Paschimottana, Ardhamatsyendra, Mayura, Jatara Parivarthana", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Which Kriya purifies the facial parts?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Neti", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "Name any 4 of the Meditative Asanas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Siddha, Padma, Vajra, Sukha", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "King of the asanas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Seershasan", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "Name any 5 Mantras of surya namaskaras?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Mitraya, Ravaye, Suryaya, Bhaanave, Khagaya ...", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "Name any four Primary Asanas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Uttanapada, Shalaba, Vakra, Bhujanga, Pawana mukta,laghu jataraparivarhtana", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "Which kriya cures skin diseases?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Vasthra Dhouthi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "Which asan helps to control diabetes?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Paschimottana, Ardha matsyendra, Mayura, Jataraparivarthana", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: " Which pranayama helps to cool the body?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Seethali ,Seethkari", is_answered: false },
	{ id: 12, question: " Which asan controls emotions?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sashanaka", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Four-Human Physiology", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "How many breaths normal person can take in a minute?", type: "BLANK", answer: "15-18 times", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "Ductless glands are known as", type: "BLANK", answer: "Endocrine system", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "Length of human digestive track in metres ?", type: "BLANK", answer: "9 metres", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Which gland helps for growth?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Thyroid", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "How many muscles are there in human body?", type: "BLANK", answer: "600", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "Capacity air of human lungs?", type: "BLANK", answer: "5 litres", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "Which hormone helps for growth?", type: "BLANK", answer: "thyroxin", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "Expand D.N.A. ?", type: "BLANK", answer: "de oxy ribo nucleic acid", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "Where is blood produced?", type: "BLANK", answer: "bone marrow", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "How many vertebrae are there in the back bone ?", type: "BLANK", answer: "33", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "How many chambers are there in the heart?", type: "BLANK", answer: "4", is_answered: false },
	{ id: 12, question: "How much time ovum can live ?", type: "BLANK", answer: "24 hours", is_answered: false },
	{ id: 13, question: "Which disease occurs due to iron deficiency?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Anemia", is_answered: false },
	{ id: 14, question: "Which organ purifies liquid ailments in blood?", type: "BLANK", answer: "kidneys", is_answered: false },
	{ id: 15, question: "Which acid helps to digest food in our stomach?", type: "BLANK", answer: "hcl", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Five-GK", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "WHICH DAY is known as International Yoga day?", type: "BLANK", answer: "June 21st", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "Where is the W.H.O. s office located?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Jeneva", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "Who is our central finance minister?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Nirmala Sitharaman", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Capital Austria?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Vienna", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "First world war occurred in?", type: "BLANK", answer: "1914 to 1918", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "Who was known as Andhra Sivaji?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Parvataneni veerayya chowdary", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "Who is the first gymnast participating in Olympics from India?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Deepa Karmakar", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "Give an example for direct tax.", type: "BLANK", answer: "income tax", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "Chief justice of India is appointed by", type: "BLANK", answer: "President of India", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "Who was daughter of Ganapatideva of Kaakateeyas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Rani Rudramadevi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "In which state the sun rises first in india", type: "BLANK", answer: "Arunachal Pradesh", is_answered: false },
    { id: 12, question: "Capital of Lakshadweep", type: "BLANK", answer: "kavaratti", is_answered: false },
    { id: 13, question: "Which desert located in Australia?", type: "BLANK", answer: "The great Australian desert", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Six-Books and Authors", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "“Amukta Malyada” was written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sri Krishnadevaraya", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "“Vision 2020” written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "APJ Abdul kallam", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "“The Insider” written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "PV Narasimharao", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Who was known as Indian Shakesphere?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Kalidasu", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "Say the title of Tikkana of Kavitrayam", type: "BLANK", answer: "Kavi Brahma, Ubhaya kavimitrudu", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "Who wrote “Bhagavata” in Telugu", type: "BLANK", answer: "Subhashitalu” in Sanskrit written by", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "“Sumati sataka” written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "Bhaddena", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "“ Maa Telugu Talliki Malli Poo Dhanda” written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "Shankarambadi Sundaracharyulu", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "“ Gitanjali” written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "Ravindranadh Tagore", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "“ Maha Prastanam”", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sri Sri", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "“ Veyyi Padagalu” written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "Vishwanada Sayanarayana", is_answered: false },
    { id: 12, question: " “ Kanya Sulkam “ written  by", type: "BLANK", answer: "Gurajada Appa Rao", is_answered: false },
    { id: 13, question: "“My Experiments with Truth” written by", type: "BLANK", answer: "MK Gandhi", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Seven-Great Personalities of India", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "Who is Missile man of India", type: "BLANK", answer: "Dr. APJ. Abdul Kalaam", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "Who wrote Indian Pledge ", type: "BLANK", answer: "P.V.Subbarao", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "Who started Bhoodhana Udyamam? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Vinobhabhaave", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Title given to Tanguturi Prakasam Pantulugaru? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Andhra Kesari", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "Who designed Indian National flag? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Pingala venkayya", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "Who was the Prime Minister from Telugu states served India? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "P.V.Narasimharao", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "Who was awarded Padmasri for his contribution to nature by planting more than crore trees? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Janaki ramayya (chetla ramayya)", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "Who was the first recipient of Paramaveera chakra?", type: "BLANK", answer: " Major Somanadh Sarma", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "Kargil war broke out in which year", type: "BLANK", answer: "1999", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "The women from East Godavari district, who was honored by British King?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Dokka Sitamma", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "Which Indian won Nobel prize for peace in the year 2014? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "kailash Sathyaarthi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 12, question: "Who gave the name Vivekananda to Narendra? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Balagangadar Tilak", is_answered: false },
    { id: 13, question: "Who is Statue of Unity?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sardar Vallabai Patel", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Eight-Sports and Games", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "What is the state sport of Andhra Pradesh?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Kabaddi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "How many golds India won in Olympics 2020? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "India won total 7 Medals in Olympics, 2020 which is the highest medal tally from India in any Olympic including 1 Gold, 2 Silver and 4 Bronze", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "Who won the first gold medal for India in the Olympics?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Abhinav Bindra", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Where will the next Olympic Games be held?", type: "BLANK", answer: "In Paris, France, from 26 July to 11 August 2024", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "Major Dhyan Chand was famous for which sport?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hockey", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "Who is the first Indian female gymnast?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Deepa Karmakar", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: " The term ‘Dolphin Kick’ is associated with which of the following games?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Swimming", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "Name the 1st woman cricketer to appear at 6 Cricket World Cups?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Mithali Raj", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "What is called Flying Sikh?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Milka Singh", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "who was the First Indian Cricketer to bag 500 wickets in Test matches?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Anil Kumble", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "How many players are there in a rugby team?", type: "BLANK", answer: "15 players per team", is_answered: false },
    { id: 12, question: "National Game of Russia?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Chess", is_answered: false },
    { id: 13, question: "How many times has the Indian hockey team won gold in the Olympics?", type: "BLANK", answer: "8 Gold medals", is_answered: false },
    { id: 14, question: "The term ‘Back-stick’ is used in which of the following games/sports?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hockey", is_answered: false },
    { id: 15, question: "who was the first-ever badminton player from India to clinch an Olympic medal?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Saina Nehwal", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Nine", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 12, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 13, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 14, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false },
    { id: 15, question: "What is your Name?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Hello", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Ten-Science and Technology", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "What is the name of the first Indian missile?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Prithvi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "Which country has decided to leave the International Space Station by 2024?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Russia", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "What is sodium carbonate in chemical formula?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Na2CO3", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Atoms consists of?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Protons, electrons,neutrons", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "The smallest functional and structural unit of nervous system?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Neuron", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "What is chemical formula of benzene?", type: "BLANK", answer: "C6H6", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "Which chemical gas present in cooking gas?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Butane Gas", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "What is ohm's law formula?", type: "BLANK", answer: "V=IR", is_answered: false },
    { id: 9, question: "The word length of computer is measured in?", type: "BLANK", answer: "bits", is_answered: false },
    { id: 10, question: "Which scientist discovered the element radium", type: "BLANK", answer: "Madam cury", is_answered: false },
    { id: 11, question: "What is Ph of human blood?", type: "BLANK", answer: "7.25", is_answered: false },
    { id: 12, question: "The element used in light bulbs to produce light is?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Tungsten", is_answered: false }]
    
  },
  {
    roundTitle: "Round Eleven", questions: [{ id: 1, question: "What is the Meaning of bharat? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Intrest in knowledge", is_answered: false },
    { id: 2, question: "Who did first surgery on earth ? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sage Sushruta", is_answered: false },
    { id: 3, question: "Knowledge of herbs, medicines and sugery is found in which sastra?", type: "BLANK", answer: "Ayurveda", is_answered: false },
    { id: 4, question: "Who authored vimana sastra book ? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sage Bharadwaja", is_answered: false },
    { id: 5, question: "Hanging pillars are placed in which temple ? ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Lepakshi", is_answered: false },
    { id: 6, question: "First encyclopedia was authored by ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Sage Valmiki", is_answered: false },
    { id: 7, question: "Sapta swara mandapa located in ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Madhurai temple Meenakshi amman", is_answered: false },
    { id: 8, question: "World’s first dam was named as ", type: "BLANK", answer: "Kallanai Dam", is_answered: false }]
    
  }
]